人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  肉松
翻譯  妖精希亞
翻譯  小飯
翻譯  沫沫
翻譯  丶Charl
翻譯  ET外星人
時間軸  Jessie
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第六集
中國提供40%的救市金
China provides 40% of the bailout,
國際貨幣基金組織再提供40%
the IMF provides another 40%
一個美中能源企業的聯盟
and a consortium of American and Chinese energy companies
解決剩下的20%
tackles the remaining 20%,
我們以開采權作為交換
in exchange for which they get drilling rights.
美方只用拿出八千億中的一千五百億
The US would only have to contribute 150 of the $800 billion.
俄羅斯企業會監督生產
Russian companies would oversee production
獲取一小部分收益
and get a slice of the revenues.
這些是擬開發區
These are the proposed development zones.
我們割讓了開采權嗎
We split the drilling rights?
是的  先生  中國出了更多錢
Yes, sir. China puts in more money,
我們就拿出我們的開采技術
but we contribute our drilling technology.
分享技術真的好嗎
Should we really be sharing that?
他們早就想從我們這兒偷學了
They're already trying to hack it from us.
佩特羅夫同意了嗎
Has Petrov agreed to this?
我打算在
I'm planning to propose
德國勃蘭登堡的七國峰會上跟他提
it to him in Brandenburg at the G7 Summit.
我們已邀請俄羅斯和中國參加
We've invited Russia and China to attend,
但國會批準前
but we didn't wanna move forward
我們不想采取進一步行動
until we had congressional approval.
-鮑勃  -我們該私下談
- Bob? - We should discuss privately.
你要親自去勃蘭登堡嗎
You're going to Brandenburg yourself?
如果他的病情繼續惡化
If his health continues to worsen--
之后再看情況
We'll assess as we get closer,
但如果情況悲觀我就不去
but, no, I'll stay here if it looks dire.
我們應該起草撥款申請
We should probably draft an appropriation
以防需要舉辦國葬
in case we need to pay for a state funeral.
-道格  -部長女士
- Doug. - Madam Secretary.
我可以去白宮的
I could've come to the White House.
梅瑞迪斯·李
衛生和人類服務部部長
器官供應組織要聽命于你
The organ network, it answers to you.
說對了一半  從監管方面來說...
Yes and no. Uh, in a regulatory capacity--
你有權力調整器官接受人名單
You have the power to modify the recipient list.
順序由供應組織決定
That's up to the network.
他們有專家委員會...
They have an expert committee that--
總統的生命不能由一個委員會決定
The president's life isn't going to be decided by a committee.
我給你看點東西
Let me show you something.
他昨天是第三位  第一位已經移植了
He was number three yesterday. Number one got a transplant.
安東尼·莫雷蒂
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
總統現在是第二位  他活的機會很大
Makes the president number two. His chances are very good.
但這個安東尼·莫雷蒂再過幾小時就要死了
But this man, Anthony Moretti, he's just hours away from dying.
安東尼·莫雷蒂
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
那就讓他死
Then let him die.
我不會這么做的
I'm not doing this.
不僅違法  也有違道德
It's not just the law. It's the ethics--
那就改變你的道德標準
Then change your ethics.
不然你就辭職  讓副部長打這個電話
Or you can resign, and your deputy can make this call.
如果他不愿意  那他也辭職
And if he won't, then he can resign, too.
我會把這個部門翻個底朝天  找到我需要的人
I will strip away this entire department until I find who I need.
打電話吧
Now make the call.
波利跳
-好  我上去了  -你用過嗎
- Okay, I'm on. - You ever use it?
不  我一般用谷歌
No, I use Google.
它市場份額很小
Uh, it's a small market share,
但一個月仍有數十億次搜索
but still, it's billions of searches a month.
如果一個候選人有更多點擊量
Now, what if a certain candidate got more hits,
排名更靠前
was ranked higher,
正面報道多過負面報道呢
more positive coverage favored over negative coverage?
如果那個候選人是威廉·康威呢
What if that candidate was William Conway?
操縱搜索結果  公眾會與他們反目的
Manipulating searches? The public would turn on them.
幫他們拉到了上百萬的選票
It gets them millions of votes.
能弄到確鑿證據嗎
Can you get me solid proof?
我不會參與這樣的事
Well, I am not getting involved in something like this.
我只會作為朋友  給你友善的建議
What I will give you is advice as a friend.
別把一年的時光浪費在安德伍德夫婦身上
Don't waste a year of your life on the Underwoods.
他們已經輸掉了競選
They've already lost the election
而且自己還沒有意識到
and they don't even realize it.
我知道你只是想幫忙
I know you're only trying to help,
也明白你肯定很擔心
and I'm sure you must feel frightened
弗蘭克的情況
about Frank's condition--
你沒必要拐彎抹角  凱茜
You don't have to be delicate, Cathy.
我希望你不要干涉我的工作
I'd like you to let me do my job.
中國不能成為談判的核心
China cannot be at the center of this negotiation,
雷蒙德·塔斯克也不行
or Raymond Tusk.
把石油公司牽扯進來
Involving the oil companies
是我們贏得共和黨支持的唯一辦法
is the only shot we have at winning Republican support.
還記得那次玩啤酒乒乓球  你放水讓我贏嗎
Do you remember when we played beer pong and you let me win?
我們兩個就坐在那邊
The two of us were sitting right over there,
那兩張椅子上
in those two chairs,
你征求了我的意見
and you asked me for my advice.
那是一條好建議
It was good advice.
你也接受了  我不明白你現在為什么不肯接受
And you listened to it. I don't know why you won't now.
你上次提的是建設性意見  這次卻不是
You were proposing a way forward. This time you're not.
與你不同  我是由參議院委任的
Well, unlike you, my nomination was confirmed by the Senate,
因為他們相信我知道自己在做什么
because they believed I knew what I was doing.
很抱歉  克萊爾  但在我看來
Forgive me, Claire, but it seems to me
你正在利用現在的局面  行使一些
that you are taking advantage of the situation to assert authority
-你無權行使的權力  -凱茜
- you don't have a right to assert. - Cathy,
弗蘭西斯現在不在
you don't have Francis right now.
我是你的最佳選擇
I'm the best thing you've got,
請與我共同解決這個問題吧
so please work with me on this.
國會不會批準的
Congress will never approve this.
你在浪費大家的時間
You're just wasting everybody's time.
共和黨會支持的
The Republicans will get in line.
不是共和黨  是民主黨
Not the Republicans, the Democrats.
我跟杰姬·夏普談過
I spoke to Jackie Sharp.
當她得知是你制定了這個計劃...
When she heard you developed this plan...
她是個厲害的女人  克萊爾  而且很有說服力
She's a formidable woman, Claire, and very persuasive.
-雷米·丹頓  -雷米  我們得談談杰姬
- Remy Danton. - Remy, we need to talk about Jackie.
多美的夜晚
Such a nice night.
我們出去走走吧
Let's go somewhere outside.
你想去哪
And where do you wanna go?
帶我去海灣吧
Take me to the bay.
我們去裸泳
We'll go skinny-dipping.
你不是只有幾個小時時間嗎
I thought you only had a couple hours.
我可以找到借口的
I'll make up some excuse.
我在酒店待膩了
I'm sick of hotel rooms.
咱倆明天還有事呢
We both got a big day tomorrow.
你怎么這么掃興
Why are you being no fun?
因為你要攪黃我的法案
Because you're trying to kill my bill.
你不是想見我  你是來游說我的
You didn't wanna see me. You wanted to lobby me.
-杰姬  -是誰告訴你我反對的
- Jackie, listen. - Who told you I was against it?
博奇的幕僚長
Birch's Chief of Staff.
我相信你能從中撈到不少錢  但是...
Well, I'm sure you stand to make a lot of money on this, but--
不是因為錢
It's not about the money.
克萊爾不是靠錢說服你的嗎
Isn't that how Claire convinced you?
我今晚不想談
I just wanted to leave it tonight.
我不想沖你發火
I didn't wanna be mad at you.
我只想
I just wanted...
我不明白你為什么要幫她
I don't understand why you're helping her.
你得讓博奇同意
You've gotta get Birch on board.
安德伍德夫婦欺騙過我
The Underwoods have lied to me,
利用過我  還試圖威脅我
they've used me, they've tried to intimidate me.
我不知道克萊爾想干什么
I don't know what Claire's up to,
但我決不會坐以待斃
but I'm not gonna let it happen without a fight,
而且國務院都已經反對了
not with the State Department against it.
克萊爾知道了
Claire knows.
我們倆的事
About you and me.
她有我們的照片
She got photographs
多次同時離開同一家酒店
of us leaving the same hotel at the same time, multiple occasions.
送我回我車上
Take me back to my car.
-杰姬  聽我說  -請掉頭
- Jackie, listen... - Turn around now, please.
所以我最近沒怎么聯系你
It's the reason I haven't been in touch.
我想保護你...
I wanted to protect you...
-但是她提出了  -我不想談這個
- but she's making-- - I don't wanna talk about it.
停車  讓我下去  或者送我回去
Just stop the car and let me out or drive me back.
我送你回去
I'll take you back.
再一兩天
A day or two.
我們沒法提前知道  總統先生
We might not have much warning, Mr. President.
肝臟如此接近衰竭
When the liver is this close to failure,
一切都有可能突然發生
things can happen suddenly.
你們應該做好準備
You should be prepared.
-他的手是怎么回事  -那是撲翼樣震顫
- What's happening with his hands? - It's called asterixis.
當身體無法排除氨時就會發生這種情況
It happens when the body can't clear ammonia.
謝謝你  撒克遜醫生
Thank you, Dr. Saxon.
我不去勃蘭登堡了
I'm not going to Brandenburg.
不  你必須去
No, you have to.
-凱茜會代表我談判  -在這事上我不信任她
- Cathy will negotiate on my behalf. - I don't trust her on this.
我們必須冒這個險
That's a risk we'll have to take.
我不能冒的險  是總統去世時我在海外
The risk I won't take is being overseas if the president dies.
我們都不知道國會
We don't even know if Congress
會不會批準救市計劃的撥款
will approve the appropriation for the bailout.
他們會批準的  我會確保他們批準
They will approve it. I'll make sure they do.
你現在不該擔心這個  克萊爾
You shouldn't be worrying about this now, Claire.
你應該全心關注弗蘭克
You should be focused on Frank.
我們得給他上呼吸機
We need to put him on the ventilator
保護他的呼吸道
to protect his airways.
您該走了  夫人  去休息一下
You should go, ma'am. Go get some rest.
-現在不是時候  莉安  -非常緊急
- Now's not a good time, LeAnn. - This can't wait.
-怎么了  -波利跳
- What is it? - Pollyhop.
-搜索引擎嗎  -康威在跟他們合作
- The search engine? - Conway is working with them.
他們可以操縱人們搜索的東西
They can manipulate what people search for.
給了他們巨大優勢
It gives them a huge advantage--
等等  慢點  這是什么意思
Wait, slow down. What does this mean?
意思是我們輸了
It means that we lose.
康威的名字  他的照片
Conway's name, his image,
他們可以控制人們看到什么  強迫人們看
they can control what people see. They can force-feed it.
即便他們不那么做
Even if they're not doing that,
即便他們只是在追蹤用戶  也足以打敗我們了
even if they're just tracking users, it's enough to beat us.
你知道人們在搜索什么  就知道一切
You know what people are searching for, you know everything,
他們的希望  恐懼
their hopes, their fears,
他們半夜盯著天花板時
what they're thinking about when they're staring at the ceiling
腦袋里在想什么
in the middle of the night.
-誰告訴你的  -我信任的人
- Who told you this? - Someone I trust.
我現在不能處理這件事
I can't deal with this right now.
我們得想點辦法  克萊爾  否則大選
We have to do something, Claire, or the election--
莉安  我丈夫剛剛痙攣發作
LeAnn, my husband just had a seizure.
恐怕都不能競選了
There may not even be an election.
抱歉  我...
I'm sorry. I--
如果弗蘭西斯挺過來了  我們到時再處理
If Francis survives, we will deal with this then.
現在  我需要全心關注我眼前的事
Right now, I need to focus on what's right in front of me.
沒有任何犯罪行為
There was no criminal wrongdoing.
這我們理解  但為什么要冒險呢
That we can fathom. But why take the chance?
因為保持沉默會讓我看上去有罪
Because pleading the Fifth makes it look like I broke the law.
我同意
I agree.
我會說出真相  我會承認
So I'll tell the truth. I'll own it.
是的  你沒有跟他見過面
Yes, that you didn't meet with him.
你是說...
Are you suggesting that--
司法部長和希瑟各執一詞
It's the Attorney General's word against Heather's.
作為你的律師  我不能參與這個對話
As your lawyer, I can't be part of this conversation.
我們還是能贏得競選的
We can still win this campaign.
我去大廳等你
I'll be in the lobby.
我會支持你的說法
I'll back you up.
安保人員只看見我和古德溫一起
The security detail only saw me and Goodwin together,
沒看見你和他
not the two of you.
我要宣誓作證的
This is under oath.
安德伍德的人是想抹黑我們
Underwood's people are trying to smear us.
這場競選的全部意義
The whole point of this campaign
就是做與安德伍德截然不同的人
was to be the opposite of Underwood.
我以為你想要這個的
I thought you wanted this.
如果要犯法就不行
Not if it means breaking the law.
你覺得換作他  還會有這種猶豫嗎
Do you think he'd even be having this conversation?
你是真正在意法律的  希瑟
You actually care about the law, Heather...
所以該由你來做總統
which is why you need to be president.
-安德伍德夫人  -鮑勃  我不知道...
- Mrs. Underwood. - Bob, I didn't realize--
少數黨領袖和我正在討論救市計劃
The Leader and I were just discussing the bailout package.
布萊斯總統要我強調一下
President Blythe just wanted me to stress
民主黨人當前團結一致的重要性
how important it is that the Democrats stick together right now
弗蘭西斯還在...
with Francis being--
不必如此
There's no need.
我剛給議長打了電話  安排緊急投票
I just called the Speaker to schedule an emergency vote.
我相信總統會很滿意的
I'm sure the President will be pleased.
-弗蘭克怎么樣  -他還撐著
- How's Frank? - He's hanging in there.
你一定想快點回醫院
I'm sure you wanna get back to the hospital.
但謝謝你親自前來
But thank you for making the personal visit.
牽掛和祈禱與你同在  克萊爾
Thoughts and prayers, Claire.
謝謝你  鮑勃
Thank you, Bob.
我送你出去
I'll walk you out.
失陪一下  領袖
Excuse me, Leader.
你是來威脅我的
You came here to threaten me.
我們不必不和的  杰姬
We don't need to be at odds, Jackie.
你打算每次遭遇我的反對
Do you plan on hanging this over my head
都拿這個來威脅我嗎
every time I try to oppose you?
你自己不小心  可怪不得我
You can't fault me for your sloppiness.
也就是"是"了
That's a "Yes."
只要我們是一邊的
As long as we're working together,
你就沒什么可擔心的
you have nothing to worry about.
總統先生  希望您別過于樂觀
Mr. President, I wouldn't get your hopes up.
七國集團的成員們
The members of the G7
已經因為邀請了俄羅斯而不滿了
are already ruffled because Russia was invited,
而佩特羅夫可能會利用這個機會
and Petrov may be using this opportunity
在國際社會上給我們難堪
to embarrass us in front of the international community.
什么事
Yes?
-第一夫人來了  先生  -請她進來
- The First Lady is here, sir. - Send her in.
先生  我想先完成我們的討論
Sir, I would like to finish our briefing--
第一夫人想見我  我可不能讓她等著
I'm not gonna keep the First Lady waiting if she wants to see me.
-你聽說了吧  -對  博奇幾分鐘前來電了
- I'm sure you've heard. - Yes, Birch called a few minutes ago.
我想和你一起去勃蘭登堡  凱茜
I'd like to join you in Brandenburg, Cathy.
很感謝你愿意出力
Well, I appreciate you wanting to pitch in,
但我真的認為沒這必要
but I really don't think that's necessary.
我比任何人都了解這個計劃
Well, I know this plan better than anyone.
-總統先生  -機會只有一次
- Mr. President... - There is only one shot at this.
-所有人都在場  -弗蘭克呢
- Everyone at the same table. - What about Frank?
我在勃蘭登堡能派上用場  在這里就不能了
In Brandenburg, I can be useful. I can't here.
第一夫人不能
The First Lady cannot
代表美國政府進行談判
negotiate on behalf of the United States government.
誰做代表由你決定  總統先生
The delegation is at your discretion, Mr. President.
有人支持你  或許是好事
It might be good for you to have some support.
她的在場會削弱我作為國務卿的權威
Her presence undermines my authority as Secretary of State.
凱茜  佩特羅夫非常固執  這你相信我
Cathy, Petrov is incredibly stubborn. Trust me, I know.
你為什么不愿意用上所有的資源呢
Why wouldn't you wanna have every asset available to you?
請允許我做這件事  總統先生
Allow me to do this, Mr. President.
-先生  -如果能增加勝算
- Sir-- - If it increases our chances.
會的  我保證
It will, I promise.
那就一起吧  我們把簡報過一遍
Then join us. We're going over the briefing now.
你盡力了  弗蘭克
You tried, Frank...
這已經比大多數人都強了
which is more than most people ever do.
現在  只剩下我們了
Right now, it's just us.
閉上你的眼睛
Rest your eyes.
我們有用不完的時間
We have all the time in the world.
丹尼  發生什么事了
Danny, what was that?
-丹尼  -沒事  媽媽
- Danny? - Nothing, Mom.
把門打開
Open the door.
安德伍德夫人  薩克遜醫生的電話
Mrs. Underwood? Dr. Saxon is on the line.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
喂
Hello?
晚上好  或者說早上好
Good evening, or good morning.
安德伍德總統正在準備手術
President Underwood is currently being prepped for surgery
接受肝臟移植
to receive a liver transplant.
不出意外的話
Barring any complications,
手術將耗時12到13小時
the surgery is expected to take 12 to 13 hours.
有需要的話我們會向大家更新情況
Uh, we'll update you about the progress if need be,
但在手術結束之前應該不會有什么消息了
but probably nothing more until the operation's completed.
我們可以馬上讓飛機掉頭  夫人
We can turn the plane around right now, ma'am.
你能在他手術結束之前趕回去
You'll be back before he's out of surgery.
我們應該那樣做  克萊爾
We should do that, Claire.
峰會我會遲到  但是大家能
I'll be late to the summit, but everyone will--
不  我們馬上就到了
No. We're almost there.
-我們繼續前進  -說實話  克萊爾
- We keep going. - Honestly, Claire--
-告訴機長保持航線  -是  夫人
- Inform the captain to stay on course. - Yes, ma'am.
請給我接賽斯·格雷森
Connect me with Seth Grayson, please.
他已經進去了
He's already gone in.
第一夫人在去勃蘭登堡的路上
The First Lady is currently en route to Brandenburg
手術期間不會回到華盛頓
and will not be in Washington for the surgery.
她會繼續按計劃
She will continue onto the G7 Summit
在七國峰會中協助杜蘭特國務卿
to assist Secretary Durant, as planned.
她讓我宣讀以下聲明
She asked me to read the following statement.
"不調頭對我來說是個困難的決定"
"It was a difficult decision for me not to return..."
但我了解我的丈夫  如果他醒著
But I know my husband. If he were conscious...
"他會讓我繼續前行"
"...he'd tell me to press on..."
因為支持他最好的方式就是為國效力
...that the best way to be at his side is to serve my country.
"而我在德國能比在等候室里發揮更大的作用
"And I can serve it better in Germany than in a waiting room.
如果有緊急情況  我會馬上回去"
If there's an emergency, I'll return immediately..."
但我對杰弗遜紀念醫院的
...but I have the utmost faith...
"醫療團隊有極大的信心"
"...in the medical team at Jefferson Memorial."
我在祈禱手術成功
I'm praying for a successful procedure,
我也請求你們跟我一起為我丈夫
and I ask all of you to join me in praying for my husband,
你們的總統祈禱
your president.
請就坐  鄧巴女士
Right over there, Ms. Dunbar.
你的律師會來參加嗎
Will your attorneys be joining us?
我已經讓我的律師不要來了
I've asked my attorneys not to attend.
我們得說明  為您的利益考慮...
We have to advise you that it's in your best interest--
我很清楚  摩根先生
I'm well aware, Mr. Morgan.
我不是第一次坐上這張桌子了
It's not my first time at this table.
謝謝  周主席  佩特羅夫總統
Thank you, President Zhou. President Petrov?
俄羅斯和中國一樣希望參與國際峰會
Russia shares China's desire for inclusion.
我們期待展開有成效的會談
We are looking forward to productive talks.
同時我們也要對安德伍德總統的手術
And we also want to extend our sincere best wishes
致以最真誠的祝福
for President Underwood's surgery.
我們都非常想念他
He is dearly missed at this meeting.
謝謝  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我們可以開始了嗎
So, shall we begin?
當務之急是
The most pressing order of business
國際貨幣基金組織以及美國和中國
is the joint IMF, American-Chinese debt relief package
對俄聯邦的債務減免計劃
to the Russian Federation.
在錄嗎
We're recording?
鄧巴女士  你所作的任何陳述
Ms. Dunbar, any statement you make
都將記入司法部報告  成為公共記錄
will be part of the public record as part of the DOJ report.
雖然這段錄像只是為了...
Although this video is simply for purposes of...
你可以把錄像傳給媒體
You can make the video available to the media.
我沒有什么好隱瞞的
I have nothing to hide.
你是要放棄對大眾保密的權利嗎
So you're waiving your right to keep the video from public view?
是的
I am.
司法部長說你曾向她施壓
The attorney general says you pressured her
要她追查盧卡斯·古德溫的說法
to look into Lucas Goodwin's claims--
我讀過司法部長的陳詞
I've read the attorney general's statement.
我們還得到一份來自一名年輕女性的證詞
We also have a deposition from a young woman,
是一名職員  她說古德溫
a staffer, who says Goodwin
在3月8日辛辛那提的一場活動中曾假扮志愿者
posed as a volunteer at an event in Cincinnati on March 8th.
你與古德溫先生會過面嗎
Did you meet with Mr. Goodwin?
我在每場活動上都要與上百人握手
I shake hundreds of people's hands at every event.
如果他去過辛辛那提  我有可能跟他握過手
If he was in Cincinnati, there's a chance I may have shaken his.
但要說我跟他曾單獨會面...
But the claim that he and I met one-on-one...
所以你是說你沒有見過他嗎
So you're saying you didn't meet with him?
我們有電話記錄  鄧巴女士
We have phone records, Ms. Dunbar.
你的確曾與司法部長通過話
You did speak to the attorney general.
瑪莎是我的前任上司和老友
Martha is my former boss and an old friend.
我們經常通話  她為什么要說我...
We speak frequently. Why she would claim that I...
我們要個簡單的回答  鄧巴女士
We need a simple answer, Ms. Dunbar.
你是否曾與
Did you or did you not
盧卡斯·古德溫在辛辛那提私下見面
meet with Lucas Goodwin privately in Cincinnati?
是的
Yes.
我與一名不認識的男人見了面
I met with a man I didn't know
結果發現他精神錯亂
who turned out to be unhinged.
我聯系司法部長
I contacted the attorney general
是因為她是國內頂尖的執法人員
because she's the top law enforcement official in the country
而且證人保護計劃受她管轄
and WITSEC is under her jurisdiction.
我沒做錯什么
I did nothing wrong.
告訴我們這場會面的性質
Tell us the nature of this meeting.
我要鄭重聲明
I'd like to say, for the record,
我認為這次面談是一場政治陰謀
that I think this interview is an act of political sabotage.
其目的就是要通過關聯讓我看上去有罪
Its goal is to make me look guilty by association,
但表象與事實是兩回事
but there are the way things look and the way things actually are.
我調查弗蘭克·安德伍德的時候
When I investigated Frank Underwood,
他看上去是清白的  但他并不是
he looked innocent, but he wasn't.
我無法證明  可我知道確實如此
I couldn't prove it, but I knew it to be true.
鄧巴女士
Ms. Dunbar...
你們有我跟古德溫先生會面的證據
You have proof that I met with Mr. Goodwin.
我已經承認了
I've admitted it.
這只能證明我的誠實
All that proves is that I'm honest,
不像總統那樣為了個人利益
unlike a president who would use the Department of Justice
利用司法部去攻擊他的對手
to target his political opponent for his own personal gain.
我要提醒你  女士
Let me remind you, ma'am,
總統在這次調查開始前就已陷入昏迷...
the president was unconscious when this investigation began...
不論他是否意識清醒
It doesn't matter whether he was unconscious or not,
不論他是死是活
whether he lives or dies.
為總統效力的人代表的就是他
The president is the people who work for him.
我覺得這事成不了
I don't think this is going to work.
佩特羅夫在會上說得漂亮
Petrov's talking the talk in session,
但卻不肯跟我私下見面
but he won't meet with me privately.
中國人已經準備簽字了  如果是因為這個
Chinese are ready to sign, if that's the hold-up.
跟中國人無關
It's not the Chinese.
他拒絕跟任何非國家首腦講話
He refuses to meet with anyone other than a head of state.
那就看看他愿不愿意跟總統夫人見面
Then see if he'll meet with the president's wife.
這不能改變他道德敗壞的事實
It doesn't change the fact that he is morally corrupt,
鄧巴曾與古德溫見面
承认见面  攻击总统
他也敗壞了聽命于他的機關
and he has corrupted the institutions that report to him.
所以我才要競選總統
That is why I am running for president,
因為總得有人跟他抗爭
because someone needs to fight this.
她不止跟古德溫見了面
So not only did she meet with Goodwin,
她還利用調查來攻擊
she's using the investigation to attack
這會兒正在手術臺上的總統
a president who's on the operating table as we speak.
是啊  她一直為自己辯護
Yeah, the way she keeps defending herself
只會讓陰謀論者有更多...
only gives conspiracy theorists more...
她完了
She's done.
我不是說她有參與...
Now, I'm not saying that she was involved...
毫無疑問
Without a doubt.
...但許多人正在社交媒體上...
...but many are taking to social media...
-賽斯  -你好  辛西婭
- Seth. - Hello, Cynthia.
你有沒有什么工作給我
Think you might have anything for me?
...尤其總統的支持率還...
...and certainly not a president whose approval rating...
在你們的競選團隊里
On your campaign?
是的  很諷刺
Yeah, it's ironic...
我得掛了  祝你好運
I'm gonna hang up now. Good luck.
但我覺得她是搞砸了
...but I think she may have just tanked it.
總統先生  移植手術完畢
Mr. President... the transplant's complete.
他們正在縫合刀口
Now they're closing him up.
接下來就看他能否適應新器官了
We'll see how he accepts the new organ.
也許我們該給克萊爾打個電話了
Maybe we should try and get Claire on the phone.
嗯
Yeah.
快了  我們在等他
Soon. We're waiting for him now.
好的  好  謝謝  唐納德
Okay. Okay, thank you, Donald.
-挺順利嘍  -除非他的身體排斥這個肝臟
- So it's going well? - Well, unless his body rejects the liver.
-總統先生  -安德伍德夫人
- Mr. President. - Mrs. Underwood.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我以為我們要單獨見面
I thought we were meeting alone.
作為政府的代表
As the administration's representative,
我需要參與到所有談話中
I need to participate in any conversations--
國務卿女士  我相信我的人說得很清楚了
Madam Secretary, I believe my people were very clear, hmm?
能給我們點時間嗎  凱茜
Would you give us a moment, please, Cathy?
一小會兒就好
Just a little while.
我就在外面
I'll be outside.
手術進展怎么樣
So... how is surgery going?
目前還好
So far, so good.
你一定累壞了  快坐吧  坐吧
Ah, you must be exhausted. Now, sit. Sit.
你一定更想在醫院里吧
I imagine you'd rather be at the hospital.
這事太重要了
Well, this is too important,
你又不肯跟杜蘭特國務卿談判
and you weren't going to negotiate with Secretary Durant.
你憑什么認為我會跟你談判
What makes you think I'll negotiate with you?
那不是我們坐在這里的原因嗎
Oh, well, isn't that why we're sitting here?
也許我只是想...再看到你的臉
Maybe I just wanted to... see your face again.
也許我喜歡你這張臉
Maybe I'm fond of it.
你是個美麗的女人  安德伍德夫人
You are a beautiful woman, Mrs. Underwood, hmm?
那雙唇
Those lips...
你能為我說句話嗎
Would you say something for me?
你可以說...
Would you say, um...
"你真可恥  總統先生"嗎
"Shame on you... Mr. President."
當真嗎  維克多  要重提那段不快嗎
Really, Viktor? Are we gonna dredge that up?
道個歉就行
An apology would do...
如果你想談判的話
if you want to negotiate...
如果我道歉  你就不會再尊重我了
Well, you would lose respect for me if I apologized.
沒錯
Yes.
這倒是
Yes, this is true.
我不是來旅游的  維克多
I'm not here for a sightseeing trip, Viktor.
弗蘭西斯需要一個肝臟  我需要救市
So, Francis needs a liver and I need a bailout.
-你需要什么  -我需要你同意那些條款
- What do you need? - I need for you to agree to the terms.
對啊  條款  沒錯
Oh, yes, the terms. The terms, yes.
但你為什么在這兒  而不是陪著弗蘭西斯
But why are you here... and not with Francis?
你母親生病時  你回到了她身邊
When your mother is sick, you go to her.
現在卻不在你丈夫身邊
Not your husband, hmm?
那些報道是真的嗎
Were the stories true?
出問題了嗎  克萊爾
Are there problems, Claire?
你對中國的顧慮是什么
What are your concerns with the Chinese?
有太多鉆井在敏感地區
There are too many drilling sites in sensitive areas.
對我們是個安全問題
It's a security issue to us.
你們具體擔心的是哪幾個鉆井
And what sites, in particular, are you worried about?
你熟悉各個區域嗎
Oh, you... you are familiar with the individual zones?
這是我的計劃  我完全清楚
It's my plan. I know it backwards and forwards.
這樣啊  怪不得對你這么重要
I see, so that's why it's so important to you.
因為這是你的
Because it's yours.
是這其中之一嗎
Is it one of these?
在太平洋海岸上
On the Pacific coast?
您找我  先生
You asked for me, sir?
我想盡快離開這里
I wanna get out of this place as soon as possible.
我會安排的  先生
I'll make sure of it, sir.
克萊爾在哪
Where's Claire?
她在德國
She's in Germany.
德國
Germany?
我很多事要向您匯報  總統先生
A lot to catch you up on, Mr. President.
-雷蒙德  -中國人開始擔心了
- Raymond. - The Chinese are getting skittish.
他們想知道為什么這么慢
They wanna know why it's taking so long.
如果佩特羅夫不盡快同意  他們可能會退出
Now, if Petrov doesn't agree soon, they may back out.
-謝謝  雷蒙德  -我隨時待命
- Thank you, Raymond. - I'm on standby.
我們得馬上達成協議
We need to shake hands on this.
不行  我告訴過你了  庫頁島上不能有
No. No, I told you, nothing on Sakhalin Island.
只要南端兩個區  你就可以救市了
It's two zones on the southern end. Then you have your bailout.
這樣會打開一扇我不想開的門
It opens a door I don't want to open.
他們的要求很合理了  總統先生
They're being more than reasonable, Mr. President.
合理  誰說的
Reasonable? In whose eyes?
你們和中國在掠奪西伯利亞
You and China are raping Siberia.
不是我們把你們的經濟搞砸的
We didn't run your economy into the ground.
是你自己
You did.
邁克爾·科里根上吊前
Is this how you tried to convince Michael Corrigan
你就是這么勸他的嗎
before he hung himself?
因為你現在就是在要求我這么做
Because that's what you are asking me to do,
在我自己的脖子上系個繩套
to tie the noose around my own neck.
接下來呢  黑海嗎  北極嗎
What's next? The Black Sea? The Arctic?
我不能允許中國船只
I cannot allow the Chinese ships
這么靠近我的領土
to come this close to my sovereign--
安德伍德夫人  安德伍德總統打來找您
Mrs. Underwood, President Underwood is on the line.
-他醒了嗎  -是的  夫人
- He's awake? - Yes, ma'am.
去吧  我們談完了
Go, go. We're done here.
-我現在沒空跟他通話  -安德伍德夫人
- I can't speak with him right now. - Mrs. Underwood--
我有空時會告訴你的
I will let you know when I'm available.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
你應該跟你丈夫通話
You should talk to your husband.
不達成協議  我不會離開這里的
I'm not leaving here until we have an agreement.
但你是個業余選手  克萊爾
But you're an amateur, Claire.
你飛過來  挺起胸脯
You fly in, you puff up your chest
假裝自己是總統
and you pretend to play president.
但沒了你丈夫  你又算什么呢
But what would you be without your husband?
什么也不是  只是張漂亮臉蛋
Nothing. A pretty face.
那好吧  你想演總統就演吧
So, yes, play the president if you like.
去吧  告訴中國人他們在太平洋上什么也得不到
Go. Tell the Chinese they get nothing on the Pacific.
你覺得你做得到嗎  安德伍德夫人
You think you can do that, Mrs. Underwood?
你的人民正在受苦
Your people are hurting.
最多六個月  他們就會去紅場游行
Six months at most, they're gonna be marching on Red Square.
我不想再給你留面子了
I'm done letting you have your dignity.
事實上  你就是個跪著的乞丐
The truth is you're a beggar on your knees,
我們逼你吃什么  你就得吃什么
and you will take whatever we shove down your throat.
維克多
Viktor.
接受協議  挽回面子
Take the deal. Get your dignity back.
國務卿女士
Madam Secretary.
61和67區聯合控制權
Joint control of zones 61 and 67.
我們已取得協議  只等總統同意
We've got an agreement, pending the president's approval.
他在睡覺了
Well, he's sleeping now.
他們即將把他轉移回白宮
They're moving him back to the White House soon.
-他看起來怎么樣  -我只簡單跟他聊了幾句
- And how did he seem? - I only talked to him briefly,
但是醫生說器官...目前情況良好
but the doctors say the organ is... taking well so far.
他們估計很快能恢復
They're expecting a quick recovery.
你做得非常好  總統先生
You've done an outstanding job, Mr. President.
-你也是  克萊爾  -我要去休息一會兒了
- So have you, Claire. - I'm going to try and get some rest.
當然  一路平安
Of course. Have a safe flight.
與俄羅斯達成救市協議
七國峰會
專家原本對本次峰會
Experts were pessimistic that
能否取得實質性成果并不樂觀
anything meaningful could come out of the summit.
議長辦公室送來的預算案草案
Draft of the appropriations bill from the Speaker's office.
請放在桌子上吧
Just put it on the desk, please.
凱瑟琳·杜蘭特在勃蘭登堡如是說
...Catherine Durant had this to say from Brandenburg.
佩特羅夫總統和我與中國政府
President Petrov and I worked through the night
與俄羅斯達成救市協議
俄羅斯同意石油開采計劃
通宵協商
in concert with the Chinese government
以達成協議
in order to come up with an agreement.
連同私營企業一起
Along with partners in the private sector,
美國  中國和俄羅斯將進行合作
the United States, China, and Russia will collaborate on a plan
在東西伯利亞未開發地區開采石油
to extract oil from untapped sites in eastern Siberia.
杰·夏普
恭喜
這將使石油市場和全球經濟
This will then enable a return to a more stable oil market,
發送至: 雷米·丹頓
重歸穩定
as well as a stable global economy.
為使這項計劃可行
Now, in order to make this plan viable
并減輕美國和
and mitigate any tax burden...
中國納稅人的稅收負擔
...to the American and Chinese taxpayers,
私營公司將提供大部分投資
the corporations will provide the bulk of the investment,
雷米
以及開采石油的基礎設施和技術
the, uh, infrastructure to extract the oil and the technology.
所得利潤
and then any of the profits
也將在這些公司之間
will then be distributed commensurately among
對應分配
these corporations, as well,
還包括俄羅斯政府投資的土地價值
and including the land value invested by the Russian government.
現在  我愿意接受任何提問
So at this time, I'd like to open the floor to any questions.
有很多人問我第一夫人扮演了什么角色
I'm getting a lot of questions about the First Lady's involvement.
我們就堅持說  她只是過去協助
We stick to our message that she was just there to assist.
杜蘭特國務卿才是主導
Secretary Durant led the effort.
有很多報道說她和佩特羅夫開了很長的會
There's multiple reports that she and Petrov had a long meeting.
他們不過是互相問候  就這樣
They greeted each other. That's it.
那我們否認嗎
So we deny?
總統還未批準這個方案
The President hasn't approved the plan yet.
我們要關注他的康復  而不是...
We wanna focus on his recovery, not the-
-什么事  -衛生部長找您  先生
- Yes? - Secretary of Health for you, sir.
我回頭去你辦公室找你
I'll find you in your office.
部長女士
Madam Secretary.
-我剛給你發了郵件  -稍等
- I just sent you an email. - Hold on.
這是什么
What is this?
看見照片上的父親了吧
The father you see there?
那就是我們為總統擠下去的人
That's who we bumped for the President.
他一小時前去世了
He died an hour ago.
留下兩個孩子和他深愛的妻子
Father of two, loving husband.
馬上從你的發件箱刪除
Delete it right now from your outbox.
已經刪了  但我想讓你看到他的臉
I already did, but I wanted you to see his face...
和他留下的親人
the family he left behind.
可能需要幾天時間  但我...
Well, uh, it will probably take a few days, but, uh, I'm--
我太太起來了
My wife is up.
謝謝  先生們
Thank you, gentlemen.
-安德伍德夫人  -安德伍德夫人
- Mrs. Underwood. - Mrs. Underwood.
克萊爾
Claire.
你痛嗎
Are you in a lot of pain?
忍得了
Nothing I can't handle.
密查姆怎么樣
Meechum?
我和他母親聯系過了
I spoke to his mother.
-弗蘭西斯  別...  -幫我起來
- Francis, don't... - Help me up.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
是的  這對康復有好處
Yes. It's good for the recovery.
醫生的吩咐
Doctor's orders.
他們要我每天至少下床一次
They want me on my feet at least once a day.
我們走走吧
Let's take a walk.
看看我行不行
Now, let me see if I can do it.
我得緩一緩
I need a minute.
我會批準你的方案
I'm going to approve your plan.
那方案很棒
It's a good plan.
很不容易
It was hard.
比我預想的還要難
Harder than I thought it would be.
留在我身邊吧
Stay with me.
我們一起對付他們  一直如此
It's us against them. Always.
不然還有什么意義呢
Otherwise, what's the goddamn point?
我不能  弗蘭西斯
I can't do it, Francis.
我不能回來再做第一夫人了
I can't come back and be First Lady.
不是這樣
Not that.
我之前在總統辦公室  說沒有我你什么也不是
I said you were nothing, in the Oval, without me.
應該反過來才對
It's the other way around.
必須要有所改變了
It would have to be different.
我知道
I know.
我就是這個意思
That's what I'm saying.
來吧  看你能不能走到大廳盡頭
Come on. Let's see if you can make it to the end of the hall.
■
在過去一年中  由于伊斯蘭國(ISIS)勢力擴大
巴黎遭到大規模恐怖襲擊
在反恐的共同目標下  美國和俄羅斯的合作有升溫的跡象
以美國國務卿克里為代表的美方官員
多次就反恐和敘利亞問題同俄方代表會談
雖然會談氣氛遠談不上友好  但也非劍拔弩張
雙方都希望在反恐方面有些建設性的合作
■
但整體上  俄羅斯仍然處于強勢地位
出兵敘利亞后  他們一邊打擊伊斯蘭國
但更多時間也在打擊美方支持的反政府武裝
俄軍戰機每天呼嘯而過
美軍不得不將地面特種部隊的戰略位置告之俄軍  以免遭誤傷
過去一年中  奧巴馬不止一次在國際會議上同普京碰面
雙方有過幾次面對面的會談
但從媒體報道及新聞圖片上很容易看出  兩人關系仍然十分緊張